kidsgamesheroes.com 2019-08-24

# Privacy Policy - KIDS GAMES HEROES

We respect the privacy of of all internet users. 

**Information collected**

When you visit our website we collect some information from you. We collect no personally identifiable information such as your name, address, phone number, or e-mail address unless you willingly submit it to us via registration or contact. Some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the internet, your type, or the type of computer operating system you use is collected upon your visit to our site in order to provide our advertisers with targeting information. 

If yo were sent to our site from one of our partner sites and if you get sent to one of our partners from this site a non harmful cookie is added to your internet browser. These non-malicious cookies are set to delete themselves 1-24 hours after they have been created. 

**Advertisement:**

We do show advertisement to our users, which is handled by [Google Adsense](http://adsense.google.com/), so any such concerns with our advertising, should be directed to them. 

**Google Adsense:**

* Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.   
* Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.   
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.co.uk/privacy_ads.html). 

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, if we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement. 

If site users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please [Contact Us](http://www.kidsgamesheroes.com/pages/contact-us).

## [Kids Games](http://www.kidsgamesheroes.com/)

###### Welcome to [Kids Games Heroes](http://www.kidsgamesheroes.com/), the online arcade dedicate to **flash heroes games**. Here you will find houndred of **flash games** of your favourite heroes.  
Games of Heroes as [Batman Games](http://www.kidsgamesheroes.com/batman), [Spiderman Games](http://www.kidsgamesheroes.com/spiderman), [Ben 10 Games](http://www.kidsgamesheroes.com/ben-10), [Green Lantern Games](http://www.kidsgamesheroes.com/tags/green-lantern), [Captain America Games](http://www.kidsgamesheroes.com/tags/captain-america) or [Hulk Games](http://www.kidsgamesheroes.com/tags/hulk) are some of the hero games you will enjoy here.  
[Kids Games Heroes](http://www.kidsgamesheroes.com/) is completly **free** , and you can enjoy the games directly from your browser.  
The games that you will find here, are **fun games** , **adictive games** and full of action and entretaiment, for kids, girls and not that kids.  
Also you will find games of heroes you have never heard of, as well as you favourite [cartoon heroes games](http://www.kidsgamesheroes.com/cartoon-heroes) as [Simpsons games](http://www.kidsgamesheroes.com/tags/simpsons), [Bob Sponge games](http://www.kidsgamesheroes.com/tags/sponge-bob), [Ben 10](http://www.kidsgamesheroes.com/ben-10) and many others. For the girls there are also [girls games](http://www.kidsgamesheroes.com/tags/girls-games), [dress up games](http://www.kidsgamesheroes.com/tags/dress-up), and [kissing games](http://www.kidsgamesheroes.com/tags/kissing-games). [Super Mario Games](http://www.kidsgamesheroes.com/mario-and-sonic), [Sonic Games](http://www.kidsgamesheroes.com/mario-and-sonic), [Crash Bandicoot Games](http://www.kidsgamesheroes.com/more-heroes) can also be found at [Kids Games Heroes](http://www.kidsgamesheroes.com/). If you like to think, you can also enjoy our [educational games](http://www.kidsgamesheroes.com/tags/educational), and learn and grow your brain at the same time you are having [fun playing games](http://www.kidsgamesheroes.com/).  
While [Kids Games Heroes](http://www.kidsgamesheroes.com/) is oriented to kids entretaiment, the whole family can enjoy of the **free content** of this online arcade. [Kids Games Heroes](http://www.kidsgamesheroes.com/) is proud of be able to offer you the best entrainment and if you want to have a good time, this is your place. To make sure you are enjoying to the max, we are adding new [adictive free games](http://www.kidsgamesheroes.com/) every day, check what's games are hot!!  
Thanks for playing [Kids Games Heroes](http://www.kidsgamesheroes.com/).
